Guide to the Garrett Orr Papers, circa 1873-1994, bulk 1890s-1914, 1935-1965
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
Garrett Orr papers circa 1873-1994, bulk 1890s-1914, 1935-1965
Orr, Garrett
18.5 linear feet Extent: 11,000 Items
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
RL.00976
Language: English.
Administrative Information
Online Items
Items from this collection have been described in a searchable online database: ROAD: Resource of Outdoor Advertising Descriptions
Access Restrictions
Collection is open for research.
Researchers must register and agree to copyright and privacy laws before using this collection.
All or portions of this collection may be housed off-site in Duke University's Library Service Center. There may be a 48-hour delay in obtaining these materials.
Please contact Research Services staff before visiting the David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library to use this collection.
Provenance
The Garrett Orr Papers were transferred to the David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library from Fairleigh Dickinson University in 1996 and 2000.
Biographical Note
1907 May 22 Born, Caro, Mich.
1928 Graduated from the Art Institute of Chicago; worked for several years for various newspapers and advertising agencies
circa 1933 Joined Outdoor Advertising, Inc. (OAI)
circa 1938 Became an Associate Art Director, OAI
1957 Married Janet Brewster, then-Executive Secretary of the National Society of Art Directors
1958 Became President, Art Directors Club of New York, and Art Director, OAI
1959 Became Chairman, Art Division, Sister Elizabeth Kenney Foundation Fund, a public service campaign to fight polio
1965 Won a gold medal for water colors at the 25th Annual Members Exhibition of the Art Directors Club of New York, for his painting entitled Composition No. 1
circa 1968 Retired as Art Director of OAI, to become a consultant art director
1988 July 4 Died, Montville, N.J.
Garrett Orr was a graphic artist and billboard designer. A director with Outdoor Advertising, Inc. (OAI) for over 30 years (1938-1968), Orr oversaw national outdoor advertising campaigns during a period where technological advances and a developing interstate highway system stimulated rapid growth in the U.S. outdoor advertising industry. Stan H. Henderson, President of the Georgia Outdoor Advertising Company, Inc. once said of Garrett Orr, Garry probably produced more outdoor advertising art than any other man in history.
Collection Overview
The Garrett Orr Papers document the artistic output and personal files of advertising executive Garrett Orr. Although the collection spans the years circa 1873 to 1994, the bulk of the materials fall within two main periods: the 1890s to 1914, comprising a photographic collection of old poster images; and 1930 to 1965, which approximates the span of Orr's professional life. The collection includes the original drawings, water colors and paintings produced by Orr as designs for the outdoor advertising campaigns of a wide variety of products such as Gillette razors, Ipana toothpaste (Bristol-Myers), Lucky Strikes and Viceroy cigarettes (Brown & Williamson), Mazola corn oil (Corn Products Refining Company), Seagram beverages, Verney fabrics, and White Rose tea. Also included are folders of photographs, slides and negatives of Orr's advertising work for approximately 550 companies (with index). In addition, a collection of almost 200 large-format negatives and photographs document images of 19th- and early 20th-century posters for plays, musicals, minstrel shows, circuses, and hotels. A large set of clippings files contain published examples of the work of over 100 graphic artists and illustrators contemporary with Orr, including Floyd Davis, Ronald McLeod, George Petty, Howard Scott, Ben Stahl, Jon Whitcomb, and J. Walter Wilkinson. The collection is organized into five series--the General Files Series; the Artists and Illustrators Series; the Product Files Series; the Other Photographic Materials Series; and the Sketches Series. Large-format items from the Artists and Illustrators Series and Sketches Series have been relocated to Oversize Materials.
Closely related collections held by the Rubenstein Library include: the Outdoor Advertising Association of America (OAAA) Archives; the Outdoor Advertising Association of America (OAAA) Poster Designs; the Outdoor Advertising Association of America (OAAA) Slide Library; the Duplex Advertising Company Billboard Images and Records; the Strobridge Lithographing Company Advertisements; the R.C. Maxwell Co. Records; the Howard Scott Papers; and the John Paver Papers.
Subject Headings
Orr, Garrett, 1907-1988; Davis, Floyd MacMillan, 1896-1966; McLeod, Ronald, 1897-1977; Petty, George, 1894-1975; Scott, Howard, 1902-1983; Stahl, Ben, 1910-1987; Whitcomb, Jon; Wilkinson, J. Walter (James Walter); Advertising -- Cigarettes -- United States; Advertising -- Circus -- United States; Advertising -- History; Advertising -- United States -- 19th century; Advertising -- United States -- 20th century; Advertising, Outdoor -- Posters; Advertising, Outdoor -- United States; Drawing -- 20th century; Illustrators -- United States; Minstrel shows; Musicals -- United States; Painting, American -- 20th century; Posters, American -- 19th century; Posters, American -- 20th century; Posters -- Design; Posters -- History; Black-and-white negatives; Black-and-white photographs; Color slides; Color photographs; Drawings; Paintings; Watercolors; Bristol-Myers Co. Ltd; Brown & Williamson; Corn Products Refining Company; Gillette Company; Outdoor Advertising, Inc.; Seagrams; Verney Corp; John W. Hartman Center for Sales, Advertising & Marketing History
Contents of Collection
- General Files Series, 1935-1988 and undated
  Consists primarily of clippings, correspondence and obituary notices. Also includes a collection of some of Orr's articles; his personal notes for an outdoor advertising campaign; and announcements of exhibitions and award presentations by professional organizations such as the American Institute of Graphic Arts, the Art Directors Clubs of New York and New Jersey, and the Society of Illustrators. Arranged alphabetically.
  - (Box 1)
    - Articles, 1957-1960 (Box 1)
    - Brainstorming notes for an outdoor advertising campaign, undated (Box 1)
    - Christmas cards, 1966-1975 (Box 1)
    - Correspondence, 1957-1961, 1972 and undated, (2 folders) (Box 1)
    - Exhibitions and competitions
      - 6th Annual Exhibition of Outdoor Advertising Art, 1935 (Box 1)
      - Miscellaneous, 1958-1961 and undated (Box 1)
    - List of engagements, 1959 (Box 1)
    - Magazine covers and other illustrations, 1937-1944 (Box 1)
    - News clippings, 1958-1965 (Box 1)
    - Obituary notices, 1988 (Box 1)
    - Organizations
      - American Institute for Graphic Arts (AIGA), 1956-1977 (Box 1)
      - Architectural Photographers Association, undated (Box 1)
      - Art Directors Club, New Jersey, 1967 (Box 1)
      - Art Directors Club, New York, 1965-1968 (Box 1)
      - Champion Paper brochure, undated (Box 1)
      - Creativity on Paper awards, 1968 (Box 1)
      - Design for Advertising and Industry, poster by Fred Hausman, undated (Box 1)
      - Georgia Outdoor Advertising Association brochure, undated (Box 1)
      - International Center for Communication Arts and Sciences--World Congress, 1967 (Box 1)
      - Mead Corporation annual report, 1983 (Box 1)
      - Society of Illustrators, 1968 (Box 1)
      - Type Directors Club of New York, 1967 (Box 1)
    - Professional portfolio, undated (Box 1)
    - Publications
      - Design at the San Francisco Art Institute, undated (Box 1)
      - Posters USA, American Federation of the Arts, 1957 (Box 1)
      - Subway Posters, undated (Box 1)
      - This is Outdoor Advertising, Institute of Outdoor Advertising (IOA), undated (Box 1)
      - United Seaman's Service, 1942 (Box 1)
    - Scrapbooks (Box 2)
      - Garrett Orr designs, undated (Box 2)
      - Idea book, undated (Box 2)
- Artists and Illustrators Series, 1929-1951 and undated, bulk 1935-1950
  Clippings, tear sheets and photographs of advertisements and periodical illustrations produced by approximately 127 commercial artists. Most materials date between 1935 and 1950, with a particularly strong emphasis on World War II-era illustrations. Dates for some materials could not be readily determined but have been provided where known. Materials are organized into two format-related subseries--Printed Materials and Photographs--to accommodate storage needs, and arranged alphabetically therein by artist name.
  Prominent artists featured here include: Peter Arno (best known for his New Yorker illustrations of the 1930s and 1940s); C.C. Beall (illustrator for Collier's magazine in the 1940s); Pierre Brissaud ( Wamsutta sheets, 1930s); Dean Cornwell (noted for his World War II action scenes, and his illustrations for General Motors' Fisher Bodies and Philadelphia Whiskey); Floyd Davis (creator of distinctive comic characters for Ten High Whiskey, 1930s); John Gannam (lifestyle vignettes for Pacific Mills and the U.S. Brewers Association); Earl Oliver Hurst (cover illustrations for Collier's magazine 1930s, Jantzen sportswear); Ronald McCleod (cover illustrations for Collier's 1940s, Plymouth and Texaco print advertisements); Al Parker (cover illustrations for Ladies' Home Journal 1940s-1950s); Russell Patterson (noted for his Ballyhoo magazine cover art in the 1930s; his specialty, stylized ink drawings of barely-clad female figures in comic situations, were featured on advertisements for a number of different products); George Petty (a longtime illustrator for Esquire magazine; the Petty Girls drawings were one of the most recognizable styles of pinup art in the 1930s and 1940s); Robert O. Reid ( Collier's cover art 1939-40; illustrator for Oldsmobile automobiles and Pabst Blue Ribbon beer); Howard Scott ( Saturday Evening Post cover art 1940s; advertisements for Nash automobiles and Esso oil products; researchers interested in Scott's work should also consult the Howard Scott Papers); Ben Stahl (Rogers Bros. silverware; perhaps most famous for his illustrations on the John Hancock insurance company's American Heroes advertising campaign); Jon Whitcomb, who in the 1930s and 1940s was a nearly ubiquitous illustrator for women's and family magazines such as Ladies' Home Companion, Good Housekeeping, Saturday Evening Post, and Collier's; and J. Walter Wilkinson (the OAAA campaign Make a Long Story Short, WW II Defense Bonds); original paintings by this artist are contained in Oversize Materials.
  - Printed Materials Subseries, 1929-1951 and undated
    - Alajalov, Constantin (Box 3)
      Includes covers from Vanity Fair, 1934-1935.
    - Allared, William (Box 3)
      Includes advertisement for Ford.
    - Arno, Peter, (2 folders) (Box 3)
      Includes advertisements for Gem razors and Mori; covers from New Yorker, 1935-1941.
    - Atherton, John (Box 3)
      Includes advertisements for Dow Chemical, Kinsey whiskey, National City Bank of New York, Shell Research; covers from Saturday Evening Post, 1943-1944, and Woman's Home Companion, 1939.
    - Auerbach-Levy, William (Box 3)
    - Bauman, Ernest F. (Box 3)
      Includes advertisement for Philips Petroleum.
    - Beall, C. C. (Cecil Calvert), (2 folders) (Box 3)
      Includes covers from Collier's, 1944-1946.
    - Beadle, Earnest (Box 3)
    - Bellows, George (Box 3)
    - Berman, Sam (Box 3)
    - Bernhard, Lucian (Box 3)
      Includes advertisement for Sanka.
    - Bingham, James R. (Box 3)
    - Brissaud, Pierre, (2 folders) (Box 3)
      Includes advertisement for French Line, Pall Mall, Wamsutta Sheets, Westvaco.
    - Broadhead, W. Smithson (Box 3)
    - Broadvitch, Alex (Box 3)
      Includes cover from Harper's Bazaar, 1936.
    - Brown, Elmore (Box 3)
      Includes cover from Collier's, 1944.
    - Bruehl, Anton (Box 3)
    - Bundy, Gilbert (Box 3)
    - Capp, Al (Box 3)
      Includes advertisement for Cream of Wheat.
    - Carter, Pruett (Box 3)
      Includes advertisements for Fridgidaire, Pet Milk.
    - Clark, Benton (Box 3)
    - Clark, Matt (Box 3)
      Includes advertisements for NRFA, Swift and Co..
    - Cornwall, Dean (2 folders) (Box 3)
      Includes advertisements for Early Times, Fisher/GM, Goodyear, National City Bank of New York, Pennsylvania Railroad, Philadelphia whiskey, Powers Reproductions, Seagram's gin, Wyeth's.
    - Cotton, William Henry (Box 3)
      Includes cover from New Yorker, 1937.
    - Crouch, Arthur (Box 3)
      Includes cover from Collier's, 1940.
    - Davis, Floyd MacMillan, (3 folders) (Box 3)
      Includes advertisements for Continental Can, Dixie Belle gin, Dorothy Gray, Fleischmann's, Hind's Cream, Johnny Walker Scotch, Sanka, Seagram's, Spalding, Spud Cigarettes, Talon, Ten High whiskey, Texaco, Wamsutta, WestVaco.
    - Dekk (Box 3)
    - Dorne, Albert, (2 folders) (Box 3)
      Includes advertisements for Capital Stock Fire Insurance, Bromo-Seltzer, Fels-Naptha, Fleetwood Cigarettes, Frigidaire, Imperial Whiskey, Johnson and Johnson, Mount Vernon Whiskey, Revere Copper and Brass, Sanka, Texaco, USO, World Peaceways, Wurlitzer.
    - Eaton, John (Box 3)
    - Edmundson [William?] (Box 3)
    - Erickson, Carl Oscar August (Box 3)
      Includes advertisements for Camel and French Line; covers from Vogue, 1933-1939.
    - Falter, John (Box 3)
      Includes advertisements for Arrow Shirts, Gulf; covers from Saturday Evening Post, 1944-1945.
    - Fawcett, Robert, (2 folders) (Box 3)
      Includes advertisements for Cashmere Bouquet, Dollar Steamship Line, Gruen, John Hancock, Howard Paper Mills, Mack Trucks, Pan-Am.
    - Fay, Clark (Box 3)
    - Fiene, Ernest (Box 3)
      Includes advertisement for Lucky Strike.
    - Fuller, Ralph (Box 3)
    - Gannam, John, (3 folders) (Box 4)
      Includes advertisements for Ipana Toothpaste, La Salle, Pacific Mills, St. Mary's Blankets, U.S. Brewers Foundation.
    - Georgi, Edwin, (3 folders) (Box 4)
      Includes advertisements for Bermuda Tourism, Crane's Fine Papers, Hockanum Woolens, Italian Line, Listerine, Mercury, Byron Musser, Stetson Hats, Vitamins Plus, Wamsutta, Westvaco, Woodbury Facial Soap; covers from Cosmopolitan, 1949, and Woman's Home Companion, 1935-1937.
    - Gotlieb, Jules (Box 4)
      Includes cover from Motor, 1930.
    - Grafstrom, R. [Ruth Sigrid?] (Box 4)
      Includes advertisements for Cannon Mills, Chanel, Coty, Spud Cigarettes.
    - Graham, Ed (Box 4)
    - Gustavson, Lealand R. (Box 4)
    - Harker, Richard Franklin (Box 4)
      Includes advertisements for New York Subway Advertising Company Incorporated.
    - Harris, Robert G. (Box 4)
      Includes advertisements for Cannon, Schaefer.
    - Held, John Jr. (Box 4)
    - Henland, Merton [?] (Box 4)
    - Hirschfield [Morris?] (Box 4)
      Includes covers from TV Guide and American Mercury.
    - Hoffman, Frank B. (Box 4)
    - Hollingsworth, Will (Box 4)
      Includes advertisements for Westvaco.
    - Holmgren, R. John (Box 4)
      Includes covers from Collier's, 1929-1930.
    - Hurd, Peter (Box 4)
      Includes advertisements for Lucky Strike.
    - Hurst, Earl Oliver, (4 folders) (Box 4)
      Includes advertisements for DuPont, General Electric, Jantzen, Royal Crown; covers from Collier's, 1932-1941.
    - Johnston, Scott (Box 4)
      Includes advertisements for Ford. See also Photographs Subseries.
    - Kane, Morgan (Box 4)
    - Kauffer, Macknight (Box 4)
    - Lagaita, John (Box 4)
      Includes covers from The American Magazine.
    - Lea, Tom (Box 4)
    - Leps, Erich (Box 4)
    - Marsh, Pucile Patterson (Box 4)
      Includes cover from Pictorial Review.
    - Max, Peter (Box 4)
    - Maxwell, John Alan (Box 4)
    - Mayo, Mary (Box 4)
    - McLeod, Ronald, (5 folders) (Box 4)
      Includes advertisements for Budweiser, Chevrolet, Fire Prevention Week, Niagra Mohawk, Mobil, Plymouth, Schaefer, Schenley, Texaco, U.S. Rubber Co; covers from Saturday Evening Post, 1939, Collier's, 1939-1944.
    - Nichols, Dale Nichols (Box 4)
      Includes advertisement for Certain-Teed.
    - Oberhard, William (Box 4)
    - Olson, Irving (Box 4)
    - [Orr, Garrett: see Photographs Subseries; also Sketches Series.] (Box 4)
    - Pages, Jean (Box 4)
    - Parilla, Arthur R. (Box 4)
    - Parker, Al, (2 folders) (Box 5)
      Includes advertisement for Chase and Sanborn; covers from Ladies' Home Journal, 1939-1951.
    - Parrish, Maxfield (Box 5)
      Includes advertisements for Fisk Tire and General Electric.
    - Partridge, Roi (Box 5)
    - Patterson, Russell, (2 folders) (Box 5)
      Includes advertisements for April Showers, Borden; covers from Ballyhoo, 1935.
    - Peterson, Perry (Box 5)
      Includes cover from The Illustrator.
    - Petruccelli, Antonio (Box 5)
    - Petty, George, (3 folders) (Box 5)
      Includes advertisements for Acme Beer, Airman, Best Form, Jantzen, Old Gold, Quaker Stockings; various illustrations from Esquire.
    - Phillips, John Hyde (Box 5)
      Includes covers from Saturday Evening Post, 1940-1943.
    - Price, Charles M. (Box 5)
    - Rackham, Arthur (Box 5)
    - Raleigh, Henry (Box 5)
      Includes advertisements for Maxwell House.
    - Ragan, Leslie (Box 5)
      Includes advertisements for Budd.
    - Reale, Nicholas (Box 5)
    - Reid, Robert O., (4 folders) (Box 5)
      Includes advertisements for Blue Ribbon, General Tire, Oldsmobile, Old Gold, Sealed Power; covers from Collier's, 1939-1940.
    - Rich, King (Box 5)
    - Riggs, Robert, (2 folders) (Box 5)
      Includes advertisements for Airesearch, Capehart, Curtiss Wright, Dole, IBM, National Steel, New England Mutual, Owens-Corning, Packard, Pennsylvania Railroad, Schenley, Shell, Springmaid.
    - Riley, Nicholas (Box 5)
    - Roberts, Morton (Box 5)
    - Rogers, Hubert (Box 5)
      Includes cover from Adventure.
    - Rojankovsky, Fedor (Box 5)
    - Ross, Alex (Box 5)
    - Sawyers, Martha (Box 5)
      Includes cover from Collier's.
    - Schucker, James (Box 5)
    - Schultz, Charles (Box 5)
    - Scott, Howard, (3 folders) (Box 5)
      Includes advertisements for Blue Ribbon, Delmonte, Esso, Fleetwood, Ford, Jello, Jewel, Mobil, Nabisco, Nash, Pillsbury, Popsicle, Pyro, Rath, Schaeffer, Sohio, Standard, Wonder; covers from Saturday Evening Post, 1941-1944.
    - Shepard, George (Box 5)
      Includes advertisements for Chevrolet.
    - Siebel, Fred (Box 5)
      Includes advertisements for Ford and Shell.
    - Stahl, Ben, (3 folders) (Box 5)
      Includes advertisements for Bell, Coca-Cola, Evervess, John Hancock, Kleenex, Maxwell House, Rosenblum, Rogers Bros.
    - Staehle, Albert (Box 5)
      Includes advertisements for Amoco, Atlas, Ballantine's, Dept. of Agriculture, Esso, Hiram Walker, Swan. See also Photographs Subseries.
    - Stanley, Frederick (Box 5)
      Includes advertisements for Beech-Nut gum, Fuller paint, Mobil oil; cover from Saturday Evening Post.
    - [Steinberg, Saul: see Photographs Subseries.] (Box 5)
    - Stewart, Walter (Box 5)
    - Tauss, Herb (Box 5)
    - Taylor, Fred (Box 6)
    - Tepper, Saul, (2 folders) (Box 6)
      Includes advertisements for American Petroleum Institute, B&O Railroad, Carrier, Coca-Cola, Ford, GE, GM, Goodyear, Gulf, Heinz, Kinsey, Sealtest, Stetson.
    - Tesar, Joseph (Box 6)
      Includes advertisement for Prince Albert.
    - Thiele, Herbert (Box 6)
    - Timmons, Harry L. (Box 6)
      Includes advertisement for Studebaker; cover from Collier's.
    - Ungerer, Tom (Box 6)
      Includes advertisements for New York Times.
    - Vertes, Marcel (Box 6)
      Includes advertisements for Schiaparelli; covers from Vogue and Harper's Bazaar.
    - Vickery, Robert (Box 6)
    - Von Schmidt, Harold (Box 6)
    - Weaver, R. (Box 6)
    - Webber, M.G. (Box 6)
    - Wengenroth, Stow (Box 6)
    - Whitcomb, Jon
      - Color, (5 Folders) (Box 6)
        Includes advertisements for Acme Beer, Cadillac, Chevrolet, Community Silverplate, Jantzen, Kotex, Lustre-Crme, Oneida Silver, Palmolive; covers from Collier's, 1939-1947, Saturday Evening Post, Woman's Home Companion, Famous Artist and Good Housekeeping.
      - Black and White, (4 folders) (Box 6)
        Illustrations and articles; advertisements for Community Silverplate, Jantzen, Marlboro, Mum, Toushay, Puerto Rico, Sanka, Sea Tweed, Windex.
    - Whitmore, Coby, (2 folders) (Box 6)
      Includes advertisements for Arrow Shirts, Pepsi, Philip Morris cigarettes; cover from Cosmopolitan.
    - Wickey, Harry (Box 6)
    - Wilkinson, J. Walter (Box 6)
      Includes advertisements for Defense Bonds, Esso, Ford, Outdoor Advertising. See also Oversize Folder 1.
    - Williamson, James (Box 6)
    - Williamson, J.W. (James W.), (2 folders) (Box 6)
      Includes advertisements for Arrow Shirt, Bermuda Tourism, Ford, GE, Gulf, Hockanum, Plymouth, Wamsutta, World Peaceways.
    - Wilson, Edward A. (Box 6)
      Includes advertisement for Cadillac.
    - Wilson, Mortimer (Box 6)
    - Winslow, Earl Bartrom (Box 6)
    - Wittlig, James (Box 6)
      Includes cover from Collier's Weekly.
    - Wittrup, Jack (Box 6)
      Includes advertisement for Esso.
    - Wood, Grant (Box 6)
      Includes cover from Saturday Evening Post.
    - Wyeth, Andrew (Box 6)
    - Wyeth, N.C. (Newell Convers) (Box 6)
    - Young, Chic (Box 6)
      Includes advertisement for Johns Manville.
    - Zaalburg, A. (Box 6)
      Includes cover from Fortune.
    - Unidentified artists (Box 6)
      Includes advertisements for Airlines of the U.S., AutoCar, Autolite, Belmont Radio, Borden, Capehart, CCA, Cornet Brandy, Crisco, Dodge, Dow, Eveready, High Standard, LaSalle ( General Motors), Monsanto, Packard, Revere Copper and Brass, RKO Pictures, Saks Fifth Avenue, Seagram, Seiberling, Texaco, Westvaco; covers from Time, 1943-1944. See also Photographs Subseries.
  - Photographs Subseries, undated
    - Johnston, Scott (Box 7)
      Includes advertisements for Ford. See also Printed Materials Subseries.
    - Orr, Garrett (Box 7)
      Includes advertisements for Holly Farms and Plymouth. See also Sketches Series.
    - Schultz, Charles (Box 7)
    - Staehle, Albert, (2 folders) (Box 7)
      Includes advertisements for automotive and gasoline products. See also Printed Materials Subseries.
    - Steinberg, Saul (Box 7)
      Includes advertisements for S&W coffee.
    - Various artists, (3 folders) (Box 7)
      Includes advertisements for Chevrolet, Dodge and Pontiac automobiles. See also Printed Materials Subseries
- Product Files Series, 1915-1994 and undated
  Tear sheets, clippings, proofs and photographs of both print-media and outdoor advertising displays, representing around 450 products. Dates for some materials could not be readily determined, but dates have been provided where known. Included for some products are images from the OAI pamphlet series Poster Ideas, which highlighted successful or innovative advertising campaigns along with suggested poster ideas for particular products. Not all of the advertisements included represent work by Orr, and some clippings appear to have been added after Orr's death. Materials have been arranged into two subseries--Print Advertisements and Photographs--to accommodate storage needs. In addition, the Print Advertisements Subseries has been further organized into small- and large-format sizes. There is considerable overlap between the Print Advertisements and Photographs Subseries, and researchers are advised to consult both subseries. Arranged alphabetically by product category, therein by trade name.
  - Print Advertisements Subseries, 1915-1994 and undated
    - Small Formats, 1915-1994 and undated
      - Advertising-generic images (Box 8)
        - Children featured in advertisements (also in Large-Formats category) (Box 8)
        - Christmas-related (also in Large-Formats category) (Box 8)